

Pramodini Priyadarsini

Senior Front-end Developer

Experienced Information Technology Developer with more than 7 years of working in product and service based industries skilled at Front-end web development with a strong background of professional master degree.

\bowtie	pramodinipriyadarsini@gmail.com	+601737131	in linkedin.com/in/pramodinipriyadarsini	
EDUCATION				
	outer Application Of Engineering and Tech	nnology		Rayagada, India
Bachelor of Scie Swami Vivekanar 06/2015 - 06/2018	ence nda Memorial autonomo	us college		Jagatsinghpur, India
SKILLS				
HTML5	• • •		AngularJs	••••
CSS3	• • •		Agile Methodology	••••
Bootstrap	• • •		Javascript	••••
RecatJs	• • •		ECMAScript	• • • • •
GIT	• • •		Chrome Dev Tools	••••
Redux	• • •	00	Sass/Less	• • • • •
Web Development	• • •		Mobile Development	• • 0 0 0
Jasmine	• • (000	Jira	• • • • •
SEO	• • •	00		

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Front End Developer

MAY BANK

06/2018 – Present

Kulal Lumpur, MALAYSIA

My current project is with Maybank where my role is to develop and implement react components for single based application. One of my key responsibility is to work on schema for fields through JSON format in connection with server side request and along with that i am also working on Redux, Routers, React libraries, refactoring existing codes for Upgraded UI/UX project at may bank using agile methodology.

Technologie

React Js, Redux, HTML5, Css3, Sass, Bootstrap, Grunt/Node, Type Script

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Wipro Technology

02/2016 – 10/2017 Bangalore, India

My designation was Senior Software Engineer where i worked for one of the client named "VISA". I was handling the development for multiple projects, coordinating with different teams such as Operations, Release Management, Quality assurance. Some of my achievements were enhancements to the application such as Card activation, Visa Checkout, Single Sign On etc. During the project i had worked on sprint planning, story creation and explaining to the team, Taking part in setting up test frameworks, writing test cases for the previously developed codes, involved in code documentations and code review.

Technologies

Java, React Js, Sass, Sql, Backbone Js, Grunt/Node

Senior Software Engineer

Cloudjet Labs

09/2014 – 01/2016 Bangalore, India

Cloudjet lab is a product based company worked for Mine application. As a Sr. Engineer, worked on sprint planning, story creation and explaining the stories to rest of the team members. Took part in setting up test framework and writing test cases for the previously developed code base. Also, involved in code documentation, code reviews. I have developed cross-platform mobile applications using Ionic.

Technologies

Angular js, Web Gl, Ionic, Bootstrap, Html5, Css3, Less

Front-End Developer

Nexia Digital

04/2013 – 08/2014 Bangalore, India

Nexia Lab is a website development company and i was part of multiple projects with different clients. The role was challenging for me as i had to gather requirement from clients, communicating the same to the team before and after development phase and work under tremendous pressure to meet the client's deadlines without compromising on the quality.

Technologies

HTML 5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jquery, wordPress

Web Developer

WebConnect Pvt. Ltd

06/2011 – 10/2012 Gujurat, India

I started my career with Web connect as a Junior Web Developer where i learned various technologies and involved in website development and testing activities.

Technologies

PHP, My SQL, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Javascript

PROJECTS

May Bank Behard, (06/2018 – Present)

- MayBank is a Malaysian universal bank, with key operating "home markets" of Malaysia, Singapore and Indonesia. According to the Brand Finance report, Maybank is Malaysia's most valuable bank brand, the fifth top brand in Asian and ranked 83rd in the world's most valuable bank brands.
- Integrated web service API to allow user to interface with MayBank Web application.
- Developed enhancements to the application such as debit Card activation, Overseas Transfer, Deepa Money, M2uPay integration.

VDCA WEBUI (03/2016 – 10/2017)

- The Visa Digital Commerce App (VDCA) is a mobile payment app that allows Banks to brand this service for their consumer. VDCA is just one of many digital services provided by these Banks who complement their existing online and mobile service with VDCA and a seamless consumer experience when it comes to managing their identity.
- Integrated service API to allow other bank systems to interface with this application.
- Developed enhancements to the application such as Card activation, Visa Checkout, SingleSignOn, integrating with this tools for various teams such as Operations, Release Management

VDCA - On boarding and CSR Tool (04/2016 – 08/2017)

- VDCA on boarding tool is a white label application tool provided by VISA. This tool provides net banking solution for different Banks. It has so many blended features like visa checkout, Single sign on, Visa notification service, Card Activation and many more. VDCA Customer Service Relationship (CSR) tool provided by VISA.
- Helped build this tool from scratch using React JS and a designer mock up.
- Responsible for requirements gathering and project development.

PROJECTS

Reactore (09/2014 - 01/2016)

- "Reactore" is a unique and innovative system that collaborates with a Mines's existing software applications to ensure 3600 view of Mines' resources and operations that allows mining management to resolve complex challenges, improve predictability and optimize the ore reserve.
- Worked intensely on the User Interface (HTML5, CSS3, Angular Js, JavaScript, and JQuery).
- Mobile Website Designing and Coding (Twitter Bootstrap)
- Ran regular routine tests to make sure the site worked properly with different specifications, in various browsers.
- Worked on Maps and Charts (High charts) and regular unit test cases.

Collectabillia (08/2013 - 01/2014)

- Collectabillia is an online portal in India that sells and auctions memorabilia of sporting stars.
- Worked on the web site development using technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JQuery.
- Worked with Design team in every phase of this project to satisfy client requirement.
- Devising SEO strategies based around specific keywords.

Yourdesignpick (12/2011 - 09/2012)

- YourDesignPick delivers custom designs for corporate identity, merchandise, advertisements, web layouts and social media themes along with expert PHP coding services.
- Worked on the User Interface Development using technologies like HTML, XHTML, CSS, Php, JavaScript, and JOuery.
- Gathered website requirement from client and communicate with them after every development phase

Smartinfosys (06/2012 – 09/2012)

- "Smartinfosys" is a web design and website development organization delivering Internet Consultancy, Creative Website Designs, Web Maintenance Services, Graphic Design Services, Business Identity Packages (Business Cards/Brochures/Visiting Cards/Envelops), Flash Designs, Static & Flash Templates Customization, e-Commerce Solutions etc.
- Worked on the Website Development using technologies like HTML, XHTML, CSS, Php, JavaScript, and JQuery.
- Developing website that have a consistent feel and look through all the web properties.

CERTIFICATES

Dot Net Programming Certification (08/2010 – 10/2010)

Technosoft Solution, Visakhapatnam, India

Java Programming Certification (06/2019 – 07/2009)

Interface Software, Bhubaneswar, India

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Oriya

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

REFERENCES

Yaseer Batoine, MAY BANK

"Yaseer is my Team Lead at MayBank."

Contact: +60176159404

Muruli Ganta, Cloud Jet Lab

"Muruli Ganta was one of the co-founder of Cloud Jet Lab"

Contact: +919886033590

Sruthi Mv, Nexia Lab

Contact: +918867265278

"Sruthi was one my team member at Nexia."

Manivannan Radhakrishnan, VISA

"Mani was my team leader at Visa."

Contact: +919739021732

Chitranjan Srivastva, Web Connect Pvt Ltd

"Chitaranjan was one of my team member at Web connect."

Contact: +917499525130